<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tulip Solutions</title><link>https://tulipsolutions.nl/</link><description>Recent content on Tulip Solutions</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://tulipsolutions.nl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Matching Engine</title><link>https://tulipsolutions.nl/components/matching-engine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tulipsolutions.nl/components/matching-engine/</guid><description>If you are looking to replace your current matching engine we got just what you need. Our matching engine will help you serve more customers, prevent downtime during peak hours and will increase the trust in your platform. It is build by traders for traders, leverages the latest techniques and programming languages (Rust), is fully verifiable and able to processes 300.000 orders per second.</description></item><item><title>Payment processing Engine</title><link>https://tulipsolutions.nl/components/transaction-engine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tulipsolutions.nl/components/transaction-engine/</guid><description>Our transaction engine takes care of consistency between transactions (withdraws and deposits) and user balances. It tracks the status of the transactions cryptocurrency/bank accounts and notifies the matching engine when a transaction is confirmed. The engine is modular and extendable allowing you to choose which service should sign, analyze and broadcast the transaction.</description></item><item><title>Scaling your platform</title><link>https://tulipsolutions.nl/homepage/scalability/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tulipsolutions.nl/homepage/scalability/</guid><description>With our solutions, your trading platform can handle peak loads of over 300.000 trades/sec with the added benefit of being flexible enough to handle changing customer functional requirements.</description></item><item><title>Example frontend application</title><link>https://tulipsolutions.nl/components/frontend/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tulipsolutions.nl/components/frontend/</guid><description>We provide a demonstration frontend which already contains all the functionality our components offer. It demonstrates how you can integrate the functionality into your own website or app and allows you to get started quickly.
Dark theme</description></item><item><title>Minimize the downtime of your trading platform.</title><link>https://tulipsolutions.nl/homepage/stability/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tulipsolutions.nl/homepage/stability/</guid><description>Our focus on the quality of our components, efforts to be backward compatibility and our redundant deployments, minimize the downtime of your platform.</description></item><item><title>Storage engine</title><link>https://tulipsolutions.nl/components/storage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tulipsolutions.nl/components/storage/</guid><description>Storing historical order and trade information becomes expensive and difficult to manage. Trading data is requested by various actors which require different views and it can accumulate to millions of entries per user over time. You may have started with a simple database, but can no longer serve customers with data they request while paying a ton of hosting fees to your cloud providers. Our storage solution tackles this by providing your users instant access to their data at a very low total cost of ownership for you.</description></item><item><title>Gateway</title><link>https://tulipsolutions.nl/components/api-gateway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tulipsolutions.nl/components/api-gateway/</guid><description> We experienced the issues first hand Over the past few years, we have implemented many APIs and experienced a variety of issues. Although the situation has improved, most of the exchanges still don&amp;rsquo;t offer the functionality and convenience you would expect.
We make sure traders have the best experience</description></item><item><title>Making your platform more efficient</title><link>https://tulipsolutions.nl/homepage/efficiency/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tulipsolutions.nl/homepage/efficiency/</guid><description>Our solutions reduce infrastructure complexity and associated costs. We offer flexible deployment options, complete documentation, API enabled services and no restriction on the number of markets.</description></item><item><title>Making your platform more credible</title><link>https://tulipsolutions.nl/homepage/credible/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tulipsolutions.nl/homepage/credible/</guid><description>Our solutions make sure your platform&amp;rsquo;s accounting is consistent, is auditable and verifiable. Within our components, self-trading and rounding errors do not occur.</description></item><item><title>Interested in one of our components or want to get your hands on demo infrastructure?</title><link>https://tulipsolutions.nl/homepage/calltoactioncomponents/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tulipsolutions.nl/homepage/calltoactioncomponents/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Interested in one of our services?</title><link>https://tulipsolutions.nl/homepage/calltoaction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tulipsolutions.nl/homepage/calltoaction/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>