<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tulip Solutions on Tulip solutions</title><link>https://tulipsolutions.nl/</link><description>Recent content in Tulip Solutions on Tulip solutions</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 15:37:57 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tulipsolutions.nl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Easy to integrate plug-and-play infrastructure</title><link>https://tulipsolutions.nl/services/plugplay/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tulipsolutions.nl/services/plugplay/</guid><description>Lowering the barrier Instead of incurring a lot of upfront costs in the design and development of your infrastructure we provide it for you. So you can focus on running your exchange without having to worry about the technology.
Integration We understand you already have systems in place you would like to integrate. Helping with integration and development of custom components is part of our offering. Our system is designed as such that we can easily be extended our design is discussed here.</description></item><item><title>Reliable, scalable and accessible</title><link>https://tulipsolutions.nl/services/characteristics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tulipsolutions.nl/services/characteristics/</guid><description>Scalable architecture We use micro-service to allow our infrastructure to scale up and out and server millions of users. While still able to add and upgrade new functionality with a minimal impact on availability.</description></item><item><title>A consistent API that just works</title><link>https://tulipsolutions.nl/services/consistent-api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tulipsolutions.nl/services/consistent-api/</guid><description> We experienced the issues first hand Over the past few years, we have implemented many APIs and experienced a variety of issues. Although the situation has improved, most of the exchanges still don&amp;rsquo;t offer the functionality and convenience you would expect.
We make sure traders have the best experience</description></item><item><title>contact</title><link>https://tulipsolutions.nl/who-are-we/contact/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 09:29:16 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://tulipsolutions.nl/who-are-we/contact/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>