<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Tulip Solution on Tulip solutions</title><link>/services/</link><description>Recent content in The Tulip Solution on Tulip solutions</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 11:52:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Low barrier plug-and-play infrastructure</title><link>/services/plugplay/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/services/plugplay/</guid><description>Lowering the barrier Instead of incurring a lot of upfront costs in design and development of your infrastructure we provide it for you. So you can focus on running your exchange without having to worry about the technology.
Integration We understand you already have systems in place you would like to integrate. Helping with integration and development of custom components is part of our offering. Our system is designed as such that we can easily be extended our design is discussed here.</description></item><item><title>Reliable, scalable and compliant</title><link>/services/characteristics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/services/characteristics/</guid><description>Scalable architecture Our infrastructure is composed of a multitude of micro services allowing us to horizontally scale up and out. When there is more user demand we spin up extra web service, API services or processing services depending on the type of demand. This architecture also allows us to easily add, upgrade new services and functionality without any impact the availability of our infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>A consistent API that just works</title><link>/services/consistant-api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/services/consistant-api/</guid><description> We experienced the issues first hand Over the past few years we have implemented many API&amp;rsquo;s and experienced a variety of issues. Although the situation has improved most of the exchanges still don&amp;rsquo;t offer the functionality and convenience you would expect.
We make sure traders have the best experience</description></item></channel></rss>