<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Tulip Solution on Tulip Solutions</title><link>https://tulipsolutions.nl/services/</link><description>Recent content in The Tulip Solution on Tulip Solutions</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://tulipsolutions.nl/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Easy to integrate plug-and-play infrastructure</title><link>https://tulipsolutions.nl/services/plugplay/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tulipsolutions.nl/services/plugplay/</guid><description>Lowering the barrier Instead of incurring a lot of upfront costs in the design and development of your infrastructure we provide it for you. So you can focus on running your exchange without having to worry about the technology.
Integration We understand you already have systems in place you would like to integrate. Helping with integration and development of custom components is part of our offering. Our platform is designed as such that we can easily extend it to your needs.</description></item><item><title>Reliable, scalable and accessible</title><link>https://tulipsolutions.nl/services/characteristics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tulipsolutions.nl/services/characteristics/</guid><description>Scalable architecture We use micro-service architecture to allow our infrastructure to scale up and serve millions of users. It also allows us to add new and upgrade existing functionality with a minimal impact on availability.</description></item><item><title>A consistent API that just works</title><link>https://tulipsolutions.nl/services/consistent-api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tulipsolutions.nl/services/consistent-api/</guid><description> We experienced the issues first hand Over the past few years, we have implemented many APIs and experienced a variety of issues. Although the situation has improved, most of the exchanges still don&amp;rsquo;t offer the functionality and convenience you would expect.
We make sure traders have the best experience</description></item></channel></rss>